What's up guys, hope you're doing great.
I would like to record a quick video to Zia and his team.
Zia and his team are great developers.
I'm working with them for quite a while.
We've been working on a few projects,
like implementing a custom solution for off-session payments
and one-click upsells made for WOP,
because we are using WOP as our main payment processor,
and it was hard for us to integrate that
with our funnel builder,
and Zia and his team helped us to basically
create and implement the whole flow into our system.
And now with our own backend,
we are basically processing one-click upsells,
which are boosting our cash per customer quite a lot.
So the whole project with Zia was amazing.
I have almost nothing bad to say,
like it was amazing,
like the outcome that was promised was delivered,
and not just that,
Zia also implemented some extra features
to maximize the user experience,
like refilling the email into the checkouts
and redirecting customers to failed payment pages
when the payment was declined and much more.
Then we were also working on some other stuff,
like for example, tracking improvements.
It's from what I see,
it's implemented for six days, I guess,
and the tracking score is very good.
I think it's like 97, 99%, which is absolutely phenomenal.
So yeah, if you are thinking about working with Zia
and his team, I would definitely recommend that.
Zia is a great developer,
so yeah, if you are searching for someone
very good in this field, Zia is the guy.